[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "How many assets are located in FMX High School?",
    "expected_answer": "47 in CSV, 63 in Glue"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is the type of all assets in the dataset?",
    "expected_answer": "Electrical, HVAC, Plumbing, Vehicle, Fire Safety"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What is the average replacement Asset Value of each asset?",
    "expected_answer": "12000"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Which school has the asset with Tag \"1629132 - AHU 14-ES\"?",
    "expected_answer": "FMX Elementary School"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Which manufacturer appears most frequently in the dataset?",
    "expected_answer": "Trane 9 times"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Which manufacturer (with no empty values) appears most frequently in the dataset?",
    "expected_answer": "Trane 9 times"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Which building has a unit installed on 2/20/2020?",
    "expected_answer": "FMX Middle School"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "How many unique buildings are represented in the dataset?",
    "expected_answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "How many assets have a planned replacement date after 2035?",
    "expected_answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Which assets have an estimated end-of-life in 2045 but a planned replacement before 2035?",
    "expected_answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "How many assets do not have a specified manufacturer?",
    "expected_answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What is the average remaining useful life (in years)?",
    "expected_answer": "20.06"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What percentage of assets were manufactured by Trane?",
    "expected_answer": "45"
  }
]
